[
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 7) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "36",
      "31",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 7) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "19",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 6 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "19",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "24",
      "21",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 4 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "7",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 9 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "24",
      "23",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 4 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "14",
      "9",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 3 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "32",
      "25",
      "29"
    ]
  }
]